How should the black community remember OJ Simpson?
Let's hear a take from my good friend Mark Lamont Hill.
Let's hear what he had to say.
OJ Simpson was a terrible person.
It is important that we remember that OJ Simpson was a terrible person.
Ever so often, you just, you know, you want people to just be straightforward.
You know what I mean?
Like, you really just want people to tell you how they really feel, you know?
I don't know if it's common, but I think it's a commonly held tape that Mark had.
I think one thing about this that I'm happy about is that his kids have been able to be shielded.
We haven't seen them.
Like, if they walked down the street, we wouldn't know they are where they are.
Yeah, because I haven't seen Khloe Kardashian anywhere.
You know what I mean?
Just jokes.
But also, another thing, too, to bring up is that the Goldman family,
because his estate is now going to be, you know,
we'll see if he had his papers in order and stuff like that.
The Goldman family might be able to get a settlement from his estate.
Because they never got paid, right?
They never got their money, right?
He didn't pay any of that.
Well, someone here in the chat said that they saw somewhere that OJ had his children sign an NDA.
But, you know, he's gone now, so that NDA is probably dissolvable.
So there might be some tell-all books on the horizon.
We up, we up, we up.